{"data":[{"question":"It was ________ good piece of news.","a":"such ","b":"such a","c":"so ","d":"so much","answer":"2","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun + that + result\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"That boy is ________ stupid.","a":"so ","b":"such a","c":"such ","d":"so much","answer":"1","explain":"\n- So \/ Such in exclamations:\n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural)\n+ So + adjective","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The Browns have ________ nice furniture in their house.","a":"such a ","b":"such","c":"so ","d":"so much","answer":"2","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"They were ________ huge trees.","a":"such ","b":"so","c":"such a ","d":"so much","answer":"1","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Her hair was ________ nice.","a":"so much ","b":"so","c":"such a ","d":"such","answer":"2","explain":"- So \/ Such in exclamations:\n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural)\n+ So + adjective","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"It was ________ horrible weather that we stayed in.","a":"such a ","b":"such","c":"so ","d":"so much","answer":"2","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)\n- Weather is unaccountable noun","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The furniture they have is ________ nice.","a":"such ","b":"such a","c":"so ","d":"so much","answer":"3","explain":"- So \/ Such in exclamations:\n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural)\n+ So + adjective","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"You'd better not drive in _______ awful weather.","a":"so ","b":"such a","c":"such ","d":"so much","answer":"3","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)\n- Weather is unaccountable noun","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't run ________ fast.","a":"such ","b":"such a","c":"so ","d":"so much","answer":"3","explain":"- So \/ Such in exclamations:\n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural)\n+ So + adjective","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I've never tasted ________ wonderful coffee.","a":"so ","b":"such","c":"such a ","d":"so a","answer":"2","explain":"- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)\n- Coffee is unaccountable noun","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}